skiutah.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy - Ski Utah

**Privacy Policy Statement**

This is the website of Ski Utah  
Our postal address is   
2749 E Parleys Way, Suite 310  
Salt Lake City, UT 84109

We can be reached via e-mail at info@skiutah.com, or you can reach us by telephone at 801-534-1779.

**Collection and use of non-personal information**

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).

We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page.  
We have the right to reject any user content submitted for publication.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by writing to us at the above address.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by writing to us at the above address.You may receive mailings from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by writing to us at the above address. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding requests or orders they have placed on-line. Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by writing to us at the above address.

Upon request, we provide site visitors with access to a description of information that we maintain about them.  
Consumers can access this information by writing to us at the above address.

Upon request, we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, unique identifiers.  
Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us an e-mail at the above address.

**5th and 6th Grade Passport Program**

What information is being collected?

To participate in the Passport Program, we need to know such information as your child's name, age, date of birth, parent's name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, 16 U.S.C § 6501 et seq., this Personally Identifiable information will be provided to us in the application that may be downloaded or printed from this site, and then mailed or otherwise sent to us. This information will be used by Ski Utah for purposes related to the Passport Program, including, but not limited to, enrollment, pass usage, and user preferences. Ski Utah employs appropriate security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, however, as no on-line data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, we cannot warrant or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us at our Website. If you have questions about the security of information at this website, please contact us.

Parental Consent Policy

In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without first obtaining parental consent. You acknowledge and consent by the return of the application to us and/or through use of your credit card to enroll your child in the Passport Program to our use of the Personally Identifiable information therein. If you wish to revoke consent, you may do so at any time by contacting us and revoking the consent in writing.

Notice To Children Under 13

Prior to providing any Personally Identifiable information by participating in any activity offered through our website, children under the age of 13 must have a Parent or Legal Guardian complete and return a Parental Consent Form by email to passport@skiutah.com. This consent may be revoked by the Parent or Legal Guardian at any time by contacting us in writing.

In the event children under the age of 13 are eligible, with parental consent, chose to participate in surveys or contests or other activities offered through our website, we will only collect and use information (e.g., e-mail address, mailing address, name, age) to the extent that it is necessary to administer the activity. We will never require that a child disclose more information than is necessary to participate in an activity as a condition of participation.

Who Does Ski Utah Share The Information With?

We will not disclose information collected from children under the age of 13 to third parties except as described below. We encourage parents to monitor and supervise the on-line activities of their children and to consider using parental control tools available from on-line services and software manufacturers that help guarantee a child-friendly on-line environment. These tools help prevent children from disclosing their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission.

The following Utah State ski areas are members of Ski Utah and partners in the Passport Program, and may receive personally identifiable information from Ski Utah related to the Passport Program: Snowbird, Park City Mountain, Alta Ski Area, Brighton, Solitude, Deer Valley Resort, Cherry Peak, Snowbasin, Powder Mountain, Beaver Mountain, Nordic Valley, Sundance, Eagle Point and Brian Head.

What About The Links To Other Websites?

Our website contains links to other websites on the Internet. The websites and addresses may change, and Ski Utah cannot always guarantee the content of every website for which we provide a link. Nor is Ski Utah responsible for the privacy policies or content of those other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our website and to read the privacy policy of each and every website that collects Personally Identifiable Information.

Changes to the Policy: We may change this Policy from time to time, by posting the revised Policy on our website. The changes will only apply to the personal information we collect after we have posted the revised Policy. We will attempt to notify you of any significant changes to this Policy by sending an email notice. However, it is your responsibility to check this website for updates as you will be bound by them if you choose to visit our site.

**Security of Personal Information**

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

**Opt-out**

You may choose to opt-out of targeted advertising from SkiUtah.com at any time.

If you do not want to receive targeted ads displayed by SkiUtah.com, please contact Ski Utah at the address or phone number above. When you opt-out of Ski Utah advertising in this manger, the opt-out cookie will be written to your browser.

Ski Utah must maintain the opt-out cookie on your browser in order to recognize you as an opted-out consumer.  You must opt-out again if you clear that cookie from your browser, use a different browser, or use a new computer to access the Internet.

Even when you opt-out, we will continue to receive information about you, however, we will not sue this information in an advertising program if we read an opt-out cookie on your browser. We may still display ads to you, but those ads will not be tailored based on this information.

**Third Parties**

SkiUtah.com may contain links to other third-party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites. If you have concerns about how other websites collect and use information about you, make sure to read that site’s privacy policy.

This Privacy Statement only applies to information received or collected by SkiUtah.com. SkiUtah.com does not control the privacy practices of third parties. Consumers who click on a link or advertisement, visit a third-party site, or interact with third-party content are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties, where applicable

**Statement Changes**

Our privacy policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this privacy policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.
